my_q_a = {
        '0': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question':'Name the four data types used in Python',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['Dictionary', 'List', 'Set', 'Tuple']
        },
        '1': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question': 'Which of the following is a data type used in Python',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['array', 'tuple', 'set', 'object', 'dictionary'],
            'answer': ['dictionary', 'tuple', 'set']
        },
        '2': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Name three string methods.',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['charat', 'includes', 'indexof']
        },
        '3': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question':'Name the four data types used in Python',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['Dictionary', 'List', 'Set', 'Tuple']
        },
        '4': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question': 'Which of the following is a data type used in Python',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['array', 'tuple', 'set', 'object', 'dictionary'],
            'answer': ['dictionary', 'tuple', 'set']
        },
        '5': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Name three string methods.',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['charat', 'includes', 'indexof']
        },
        '6': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question':'Name the four data types used in Python',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['Dictionary', 'List', 'Set', 'Tuple']
        },
        '7': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question': 'Which of the following is a data type used in Python',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['array', 'tuple', 'set', 'object', 'dictionary'],
            'answer': ['dictionary', 'tuple', 'set']
        },
        '8': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Name three string methods.',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['charat', 'includes', 'indexof']
        },
        '9': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question':'Name the four data types used in Python',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['Dictionary', 'List', 'Set', 'Tuple']
        },
        '10': {
            'type': 'python',
            'question': 'Which of the following is a data type used in Python',
            'description': 'Choose all that apply.',
            'choices': ['array', 'tuple', 'set', 'object', 'dictionary'],
            'answer': ['dictionary', 'tuple', 'set']
        },
        '11': {
            'type': 'javascript',
            'question': 'Name three string methods.',
            'description': 'Enter you answer below using a space or comma seperated list.',
            'answer': ['charat', 'includes', 'indexof']
        },
}
